<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>{name: &#39;Alex McCoy&#39;, siteType: &#39;Blog&#39;}</title>
    <link>https://blog.alex-mccoy.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on {name: &#39;Alex McCoy&#39;, siteType: &#39;Blog&#39;}</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Alex McCoy</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 12:01:05 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.alex-mccoy.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Books You Might Want to Read</title>
      <link>https://blog.alex-mccoy.uk/posts/books-you-might-want-to-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 12:01:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.alex-mccoy.uk/posts/books-you-might-want-to-read/</guid>
      <description>Preamble I often get asked &amp;lsquo;what books do you recommend for [insert topic here]&amp;rsquo;, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d write down in one place the books that I&amp;rsquo;ve so-far read and think are of value. I&amp;rsquo;ll keep this page updated with whatever books I think deserve adding.
Fair warning, I&amp;rsquo;ve become a bit of a No Starch Press fanboy.
The Books Title: Real World Bug Hunting
ISBN-13: 978-1-59327-861-8
Link: https://nostarch.com/bughunting
Review: The subject of bug bounty can sometimes be perceived as a black box, within the purview only of tech wizards who no-doubt dream in jargon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Spoofing: Abusing the SharePoint REST API</title>
      <link>https://blog.alex-mccoy.uk/posts/abusing-sharepoint-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 15:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.alex-mccoy.uk/posts/abusing-sharepoint-api/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Famously, Microsoft loves to make out that they love developers (developers, developers, developers). Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s this love of developers that spurred them to implement a generous range of features into their SharePoint RESI API, with the intention of enabling custom web-apps to extend default functionality.
One day, I was looking through the documentation for the PnP SharePoint Library (as you do), and I noticed a feature labelled &amp;lsquo;sendEmail&amp;rsquo;. On closer inspection, this feature allows you to send an email to anybody inside your Microsoft 365 tenancy with an arbitrary sender &amp;lsquo;name&amp;rsquo; (the actual sending address is no-reply@sharepointonline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.alex-mccoy.uk/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 13:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.alex-mccoy.uk/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Having been in the back of my mind for at least 3 years, it&amp;rsquo;s good to finally have my own space for publishing my technical pieces on the internet.
I&amp;rsquo;m not anticipating posting regularly - I expect I will only post when I have something to share as opposed to working to any schedule.
Anyway, I suppose I ought to get to writing the first real blog post. Feedback is always appreciated and I would suggest tweeting me at @AlexMcCoy41.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
